<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation - builder.swillkb.com</title>
    <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Documentation - builder.swillkb.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/</guid>
      <description>The documentation on this site is for the Plate &amp;amp; Case Builder available at builder.swillkb.com.
builder.swillkb.com The Plate &amp;amp; Case Builder (builder) is a tool to aid in the design and creation of custom keyboards. The builder generates CAD files to be cut by a laser cutter.
Keyboard layouts are created at keyboard-layout-editor.com (KLE) and the Raw data is copied.
Then the layout is pasted into the builder.
Then specify the details of the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Units &amp; Dimensions</title>
      <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/units-dimensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/units-dimensions/</guid>
      <description>Builder Units All units used by the builder are in Millimeters (mm). That includes dimensions, coordinates and output. Unfortunately, the current library I am using for exporting DXF files does not support specifying the units in the file format. Because of this, the dimensions are in mm in the drawing, but no units are exported with the DXF file. Make sure your CAD program is set to mm when you open the DXF because it will assume your default units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/features/</guid>
      <description>The builder has the following features available when creating keyboard layouts.
Plate Layout The keyboard layout is specified by using the Raw data from the keyboard-layout-editor.com (KLE) tool. The data from KLE defines the layout of the keyboard, or the footprint of the keys.
Once you have a layout specified, you can modify individual keys by adding or editing the key&amp;rsquo;s details object. This details object is a set of parameters defined inside curly brackets before the key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Tips</title>
      <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/pro-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/pro-tips/</guid>
      <description>The builder is a tool with a LOT of different options and possibilities. As a result, there are quite a few different tips and tricks that can/should be documented. If you know of additional tips which are not documented here, please contribute to the documentation.
SVG to STL Conversion If you want to 3D print a prototype of your design, you will need to convert the 2-dimensional SVG to a 3-dimensional STL file format in order for your 3D printer to be able to work with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need Help?</title>
      <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/need-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/need-help/</guid>
      <description>We try to give a pretty complete overview of the tool and its functionality on this site, but I am sure we have not covered all of your questions.
If you have questions or you would like to come and join the conversation around this tool, come say Hello in our GeekHack thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute</title>
      <link>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://builder-docs.swillkb.com/contribute/</guid>
      <description>The content of this website is maintained on Github at github.com/swill/builder-docs, please feel free to contribute. We will do our best to keep the content up-to-date with the functionality, but 100% coverage of the features will be a work in progress.
How to Contribute To contribute, you will need to fork the Github repository github.com/swill/builder-docs, and make changes in your own fork.
Changes can be done by editing the files directly in the Github UI in your fork.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>